<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Data Structure</string>


    <string-array name="insertion_choice_array">
        <item>insert at first</item>
        <item>insert at last</item>
        <item>insert at specific index</item>
        <item>insert in sorted array</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="insertion_choice_list">
        <item>insert first</item>
        <item>insert last</item>
        <item>insert at specific index</item>
        <item>insert in sorted list</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="insertion_choice_graph">
        <item>insert vertex</item>
        <item>insert edge</item>

    </string-array>


    <string-array name="deletion_choice">
        <item>delete first</item>
        <item>delete last</item>
        <item>delete from specific index</item>
        <item>delete specific item</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="deletion_choice_graph">
        <item>delete vertex</item>
        <item>delete edge</item>
    </string-array>


    <string-array name="search_choice">
        <item>linear search</item>
        <item>binary search</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="search_linked_list_choice">
        <item>search</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sort_choice">
        <item>insertion sort</item>
        <item>selection sort</item>
        <item>bubble sort</item>
        <item>quick sort</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sort_linked_list_choice">
        <item>sort</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="array"> <p><b>ARRAY</b></p><![CDATA["
An array is a collection of items stored at contiguous memory locations.It can hold a fix number of items and these items should be of the same type."]]></string>


    <string name="stack"><p><b>STACK</b></p><![CDATA["
Stack is an abstract data type that serves as a collection of elements, with two main principal operations: Push, which adds an element to the collection, and. Pop, which removes the most recently added element that was not yet removed."]]></string>



    <string name="queue"><p><b>QUEUE</b></p><![CDATA["
Queue is an abstract data type that serves as a collection of items in which only the earliest added item may be accessed. Basic operations are add (to the tail) or enqueue and delete (from the head) or dequeue."]]></string>



    <string name="linkedlist"><p><b>LINKED LIST</b></p><![CDATA["
A linked list is a linear collection of data elements whose order is not given by their physical placement in memory. Instead, each element points to the next. It is a data structure consisting of a collection of nodes which together represent a sequence."]]></string>




    <string name="tree"><p><b>TREE</b></p><![CDATA["
A tree is a abstract data type that simulates a hierarchical tree structure, with a root value and subtrees of children with a parent node, represented as a set of linked nodes."]]></string>


    <string name="graph"><p><b>GRAPH</b></p> <![CDATA["
A graph is an abstract data type that consists of V, a nonempty set of vertices (or nodes) and E, a set of edges. Each edge has either one or two vertices associated with it."]]></string>


    <!-- Strings used for fragments for navigation -->


</resources>